{
    "id": "10a636ea7498415c8f2ebe9099f2dd07",
    "title": "Determiners And Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "........................... of these authors is known to me.",
            "description": "Neither means not the one nor the other.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Either",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "da67f2c638ef4648b121c67d89de5e0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know ........................... of these authors.",
            "description": "Not either means the same as neither. Both is not used in negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "224d34c45aef449f91fbbcf99978c9d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are very ............................ good restaurants in this town.",
            "description": "Very means hardly any.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "hardly",
                "little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09f20049cd544d3f96ece35537fdd6c4"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are .............................. any good restaurants in this town.",
            "description": "Hardly any means the same as very few.",
            "answers": [
                "very few",
                "hardly",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2ffad988c29b4fe5a92e008ccf6d3a8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven't got cats ............................. dogs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nor",
                "or",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24c1e91b28ba4163850da7e8636c4c73"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have got ............................. cats ........................ dogs.",
            "description": "Neither / nor and both/and are possible here with totally opposite meanings.",
            "answers": [
                "neither, nor",
                "either, or",
                "both, and"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a550fb3bf5494d00a9a88126322a4daf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven't got ............................. cats ....................... dogs.",
            "description": "Both is not used in negative sentences. Not either means the same as neither.",
            "answers": [
                "neither, nor",
                "either, or",
                "both, and"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d759343b99e42f2b15aa37d30b7abfb"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................... the participants were given a prize.",
            "description": "Each and every are followed by singular verbs. All is followed by a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "All",
                "Every"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cda7c1adfe914599b362932032608cc8"
        },
        {
            "question": "............................ the participants was given a prize.",
            "description": "We use each of before an article. All of should be followed by a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Each",
                "All of",
                "Each of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1f33353a59ab445abf559de3532cd3d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a good friend of ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d7c55318124b4d869b6d3972454bef49"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted to kill that ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your friend",
                "friend of your",
                "friend of yours"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6ea0365c5b64435bc063a1067aa2660"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not better than ....................................",
            "description": "Object pronouns are more common after than and as.",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47da122d81e54111826db726cfe7cd3d"
        }
    ]
}